Register of the Romanov family papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Princess Tat'iana Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) of Russia papers from red trunks nos. 1-2, 1899-1945
  - Correspondence, 1899-1945
    - Wagniere, L., 1924-1938
      Box/Folder 10: 37
    - Wattroille, Alix, 1942-1944
      Box/Folder 10: 38
    - Witteveen, Maria, 1939-1942
      Box/Folder 10: 39
    - Wolrad, Prince of Schaumburg-Lippe, 1924-1929
      Box/Folder 10: 40
    - Zarubina, Iuliia, 1937
      Box/Folder 10: 41
    - Zherebkova, E., 1932-1939
      Box/Folder 10: 42
    - Zhirar, M., 1926-1933
      Box/Folder 10: 43
    - Zolotova, A., circa 1922
      Box/Folder 10: 44
  - Russian Orthodox Church in Paris and Geneva files, 1923-1940
    - Correspondence, 1922-1939 (Reel 14)
      Box/Folder 10: 45-47, 11: 1-3
    - Events and activities, programs, speeches, and notes, 1923-1942 (Reels 14-15)
      Box/Folder 11: 4-15 (Folders 4-8 on Reel 14, Folders 9-15 on Reel 15)
  - Financial documents, 1922-1943 (Reels 15-16)
    Scope and Contents note
    Box/Folder 11: 16-21 (on Reel 15), 12: 1-9 (on Reel 16)
  - Photographs, circa 1915 (Reel 16)
    Box/Folder 12: 10
    Includes image of Grand Duchess Ksenia Aleksandrovna visiting her son Prince Nikita Aleksandrovich on training ship, circa 1915.
  - Notes and drafts, 1924-1931
    Box/Folder 12: 11-12
  - Clippings, 1924-1944
    Includes nobility newspaper obituaries, 1928-1929. Arranged chronologically.
    - Death of Dowager Empress Maria Feodorovna, Grand Duke Aleksandr Mikhailovich, Grand Duchess Elizaveta Mavrikievna, and Queen Olga of Greece, 1928-1929
      Box/Folder 12: 13
    - Kidnapping of General Aleksandr Kutepov, 1930-1931
      Box/Folder 12: 14
    - Education of a Princess: A Memoir by Marie, Grand Duchess of Russia, book review, 1931
      Box/Folder 12: 15
    - Various political events, 1937-1944
      Box/Folder 12: 16
- Princess Natal'ia Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) Bagration-Mukhranskaia-Johnston correspondence from red trunk no. 3, 1922-1938
  - General, 1927-1933
    Box/Folder 12: 17
  - Elizaveta Mavrikievna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1924-1937
    Box/Folder 12: 18
  - Feodosiia, Ieromonakhinia, 1929
    Box/Folder 12: 19
  - Gavriil (Gabriel) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, 1930-1933
    Box/Folder 12: 20
  - Genkis, Ol'ga, 1931
    Box/Folder 12: 21
  - Georgii (Georgy) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, 1938 (Reel 17)
    Box/Folder 12: 22
  - Irinei, Bishop, 1931
    Box/Folder 12: 23
  - Ksenia (Xenia) Aleksandrovna, Grand Duchess of Russia, circa 1930
    Box/Folder 12: 24
  - Mordvinova, Ol'ga, circa 1930
    Box/Folder 12: 25
  - Murav'eva-Apostol, N., circa 1930
    Box/Folder 12: 26
  - Nesterovskaia, Antonina Rafailovna, 1922
    Box/Folder 12: 27
  - Nikita Aleksandrovich, Prince of Russia, 1931
    Box/Folder 12: 28
  - Nina Aleksandrovna Bagration-Mukhranskaia, Princess of Russia, 1927
    Box/Folder 12: 29
  - Orlov (Orloff), Sergei (Serge), 1929
    Box/Folder 12: 30
  - Roxroy, R., 1931
    Box/Folder 12: 31
  - Sheremeteva-Fabergé, Tat'iana, circa 1930
    Box/Folder 12: 32
  - Smirnov (Smirnoff), S., 1932-1933
    Box/Folder 12: 33
  - Teimuraz (Teymuraz) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) Bagration-Mukhranskii, Prince, 1927-1938
    Box/Folder 13: 1-4
  - Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna), Princess of Russia, 1922-1932
    Box/Folder 13: 5
  - Unidentified, 1931-1932
    Box/Folder 13: 6
- Princess Tat'iana Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) of Russia papers from red trunk no. 3, 1906-1945
  - Correspondence, 1906-1945
    - General, 1925-1939
      Box/Folder 13: 7
    - Congratulatory telegrams on the birth of Natalia and Teimuraz, and on other occasions, 1906-1915
      Box/Folder 13: 8-10
    - Adamovich, Boris, 1929-1934
      Box/Folder 13: 11
    - Dukhonina, Natal'ia, 1927
      Box/Folder 13: 12
    - Elizaveta Mavrikievna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1921-1926 (Reels 17-18)
      Box/Folder 13: 13-20 (Folders 13-16 on Reel 17, Folders 17-20 on Reel 18)
    - Gavriil (Gabriel) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, 1926-1933 (Reel 18)
      Box/Folder 13: 21-22
    - Hartmann, S., 1923-1924
      Box/Folder 13: 23
    - Korochentsov (Korochentzoff), Aleksei and Lilly, 1939
      Box/Folder 13: 24
    - Natal'ia Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) Bagration-Mukhranskaia-Johnston, Princess, 1923-1945 (Reels 18-19)
      Box/Folder 14: 1-19 (Folders 1-9 on Reel 18, Folders 10-19 on Reel 19)
    - Ol'ga, Princess of Greece and Denmark, 1939 (Reel 19)
      Box/Folder 14: 20
    - Proletov, E. and M., 1927-1929
      Box/Folder 14: 21
    - Simeon, Arkhimandrite, on the death of Grand Duchess O'lga Constantinovna (Queen Ol'ga of Greece), 1926
      Box/Folder 14: 22
    - Tarasenkov, S., 1923-1925
      Box/Folder 14: 23
    - Teimuraz (Teymuraz) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) Bagration-Mukhranskii, Prince, 1928-1942 (Reels 19-20)
      Box/Folder 14: 24-27 (Folder 24 on Reel 19, Folders 25-27 on Reel 20), 15: 1-2 (Reel 20)
    - Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna), Princess of Russia, 1923-1945 (Reel 20)
      Box/Folder 15: 3-15
    - Witteveen, Maria, 1939
      Box/Folder 15: 16
  - Financial documents, 1923-1939 (Reels 20-22)
    Box/Folder 15: 17-25 (Folder 17 on Reel 20, Folders 18-25 on Reel 21), 16: 1-6 (Folders 1-3 on Reel 21, Folders 4-6 on Reel 22)
  - Clippings, 1930-1941 (Reel 22)
    Box/Folder 16: 7-8
    Includes articles on the Yugoslav coup d'etat against Hitler and other political events. See also: Oversize materials.
- Prince Teimuraz (Teymuraz) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) Bagration correspondence from red trunk no. 3, 1924-1938
  - Bonjour-Rachevski, Julie, circa 1925
    Box/Folder 16: 9
  - Elizaveta Mavrikievna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1924
    Box/Folder 16: 10
  - Gavriil (Gabriel) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, 1938
    Box/Folder 16: 11
  - Tat'iana Konstantinovna (Constantinovna), Princess of Russia, 1934
    Box/Folder 16: 12-14
  - Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna), Princess of Russia, 1932-1934
    Box/Folder 16: 15
- Princess Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) papers from red trunk no. 3, 1913-1982
  - Photographs and negatives depicting Princess Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) at various events, 1913-1982
    Box/Folder 16: 16
    Includes miniature of Grand Duke Nicholas Konstantinovich (Constantinovich).
  - Correspondence, 1932-1934
    - "Ata" (Emma Karlovna Shadovets), nanny, 1932
      Box/Folder 16: 17
    - Christopher, Prince of Greece and Denmark, 1934
      Box/Folder 16: 18
- Princess Tat'iana Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) papers from red trunk no. 4, 1913-1953
  - Correspondence, 1913-1953
    - General, 1922-1943
      Box/Folder 16: 19-23
    - Invitations, 1924-1953
      Box/Folder 16: 24
    - Regarding Prince Nikita Aleksandrovich's relocation to Geneva, 1945
      Box/Folder 16: 25
    - Abbei, V., 1922-1924
      Box/Folder 16: 26
    - Alberi d'Enno, L., circa 1930
      Box/Folder 16: 27
    - Aleksei (Alexis) Bagration, Prince, 1945
      Box/Folder 16: 28
    - Altukhovich, V. P., 1928-1930
      Box/Folder 16: 29
    - Anastasiia, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1927 (Reel 23)
      Box/Folder 17: 1
    - Aristova, Nadezhda, 1930-1931
      Box/Folder 17: 2
    - Asperin, Gaston de Rothien, 1938-1945
      Box/Folder 17: 3
    - "Ata" (Emma Karlovna Shadovets), nanny, 1924-1938
      Box/Folder 17: 4
    - Bagration-Mukhranskaia, Mariia, 1944
      Box/Folder 17: 5
    - Bagration-Mukhranskaia (Bagration-Mukhranelli), Ol'ga, 1924
      Box/Folder 17: 6
    - Balazzi, Sofie, 1928
      Box/Folder 17: 7
    - Billo, Nicolas, 1922
      Box/Folder 17: 8
    - Blanch, A. de, 1930
      Box/Folder 17: 9
    - Boiarskaia, E., 1940
      Box/Folder 17: 10
    - Bonjour-Rachevski, Julie, 1931
      Box/Folder 17: 11
    - Borisova, Zoia, 1938
      Box/Folder 17: 12
    - Bossar, Eugenia, 1927-1945
      Box/Folder 17: 13
    - Brevern, A., 1926
      Box/Folder 17: 14
    - Bruel, E., 1928
      Box/Folder 17: 15
    - Bustras, Anna, circa 1930
      Box/Folder 17: 16
    - Butovich, Iuliia, 1924-1938
      Box/Folder 17: 17
    - Chaubert, A., 1934
      Box/Folder 17: 18
    - Chekan, Mariia, 1938
      Box/Folder 17: 19
    - Chetwynd, Augusta, 1930
      Box/Folder 17: 20
    - Chicherina-Eristova, Nadezhda, 1935
      Box/Folder 17: 21
    - Christopher, Prince of Greece and Denmark, 1926
      Box/Folder 17: 22
    - Deonna, Edmee, 1944
      Box/Folder 17: 23
    - Droin, E., 1940
      Box/Folder 17: 24
    - Dukhonina, Natal'ia, 1926-1938
      Box/Folder 17: 25
    - Elena Vladimirovna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1931-1934
      Box/Folder 17: 26
    - Elizaveta Mavrikievna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1924-1927
      Box/Folder 17: 27
    - Elsa, Duchess of Württemberg, 1927-1933
      Box/Folder 17: 28
    - Engelhard, Sofie, 1938
      Box/Folder 17: 29
    - Fabergé, Serge, 1931-1938
      Box/Folder 17: 30
    - Frederick, N., 1938
      Box/Folder 17: 31
    - Frieda, Grune, 1930
      Box/Folder 17: 32
    - Frohling, Clare, 1944
      Box/Folder 17: 33
    - Prince Gavriil (Gabriel) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), 1924-1944
      Box/Folder 17: 34-35
    - Gibzattel, S., 1928-1930
      Box/Folder 17: 36
    - Georgii (Georgy) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, 1923-1938
      Box/Folder 17: 37
    - Gillard, Pierre and A., 1938-1944
      Box/Folder 17: 38
    - Glaser, Aleksandra Andreevna, 1924-1944 (Reel 24)
      Box/Folder 17: 39
    - Golitsyna, Anna, 1928-1930
      Box/Folder 17: 40
    - Gonseth, Henri, 1927-1931
      Box/Folder 17: 41
    - Gorchakov family, 1930
      Box/Folder 17: 42
    - Goriachkovskaia, Kseniia, 1930
      Box/Folder 17: 43
    - Gott, U., 1921
      Box/Folder 17: 44
    - Guilerat, Cecile, 1938-1942
      Box/Folder 17: 45
    - Hagedorn-Kater, Lily, 1938
      Box/Folder 17: 46
    - Heitamann, A., 1938
      Box/Folder 17: 47
    - Helen, Princess of Serbia, 1938
      Box/Folder 17: 48
    - Hoffmann-Sokolovskaia, Elena, 1938-1945
      Box/Folder 17: 49
    - Horneffer, S Ch., 1931-1944
      Box/Folder 17: 50
    - Hoyningen-Huene, Aleksandr (Alexander) von, 1927
      Box/Folder 17: 51
    - Ignat'ev, L., 1924-1938
      Box/Folder 18: 1
    - Ignatovskii (Ignatovsky), Aleksandr (Alexandre), 1928
      Box/Folder 18: 2
    - Iraklii (Irakli) Bagration, Prince of Mukhrani, 1938
      Box/Folder 18: 3
    - Jonston, Emma, 1944
      Box/Folder 18: 4
    - Kantakuzin, Konstantin and Ekaterina, 1924-1938
      Box/Folder 18: 5
    - Kaubish, Aleksandra, 1927
      Box/Folder 18: 6
    - Kauffman, Reginald Wright, 1924-1930
      Box/Folder 18: 7
    - Kazakovskii, Nikolai Ivanovich, 1922
      Box/Folder 18: 8
    - Khvoshchinskaia, Aleksandra (Ksana), 1938-1939
      Box/Folder 18: 9
    - Kniazhevich, Aleksandra, 1938
      Box/Folder 18: 10
    - Kolchev, Leonid, 1924-1927
      Box/Folder 18: 11
    - Kolemin, I., 1943
      Box/Folder 18: 12
    - Koniar, Aleksandra, 1924
      Box/Folder 18: 13
    - Konstantin (Constantin) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, 1913
      Box/Folder 18: 14
    - Konstantinovskii, E., 1928
      Box/Folder 18: 15
    - Korf (Korff), S., 1922-1930
      Box/Folder 18: 16
    - Korob'in, G. and E., 1938
      Box/Folder 18: 17
    - Korochentsov (Korochentzoff), Aleksei and Lilly, 1924-1938
      Box/Folder 18: 18
    - Kovalevskii, M, 1931-1936
      Box/Folder 18: 19
    - Kruzenshtern, Ada, 1930-1939
      Box/Folder 18: 20
    - Ksenia (Xenia) Aleksandrovna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1927-1939
      Box/Folder 18: 21
    - Kugusheva, S., 1924-1938
      Box/Folder 18: 22
    - Kutaisova, M., 1927
      Box/Folder 18: 23
    - Kvasnevskaia, M., 1938
      Box/Folder 18: 24
    - Lebmann, M., 1938
      Box/Folder 18: 25
    - Leikhtenbergskaia, Mariia, 1927-1938
      Box/Folder 18: 26
    - Levitskaia, Mariia, 1927-1938
      Box/Folder 18: 27
    - Lipskii (Lipsky), M., 1945
      Box/Folder 18: 28
    - Lobanova-Rostovskaia, E., 1927-1938
      Box/Folder 18: 29
    - Lodyzhenskaia, Nina and Lodyzhenskii Iurii, 1930-1940
      Box/Folder 18: 30
    - Makneva, N., circa 1930
      Box/Folder 18: 31
    - Mariia Illarionovna Romanova (Vorontsova-Dashkova), Princess of Russia, 1930-1945
      Box/Folder 18: 32
    - Martin, Jean, 1938
      Box/Folder 18: 33
    - Masset, S., 1942
      Box/Folder 18: 34
    - Meiendorff, Alina, 1930-1938
      Box/Folder 18: 35
    - Meiendorff, Helene, 1925
      Box/Folder 18: 36
    - Meuron, Isabella de, 1939
      Box/Folder 18: 37
    - Militsa (Militza) Nikolaevna, Grand Duchess of Russia, circa 1930
      Box/Folder 18: 38
    - Miller, Zoia, 1930
      Box/Folder 18: 39
    - Mirski (Sviatopolk-Mirskaia), Greta, 1930-1945
      Box/Folder 18: 40
    - Mitchell (Eagley), Maria M., 1938
      Box/Folder 18: 41
    - Murav'eva-Apostol, N., 1929-1945
      Box/Folder 18: 42
    - Narmont, Valentina and Valerii, 1928
      Box/Folder 18: 43
    - Natal'ia Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) Bagration-Mukhranskaia-Johnston, Princess, 1926-1930
      Box/Folder 18: 44-45
    - Nef, Ol'ga, 1925-1939 (Reel 25)
      Box/Folder 18: 46
    - Nesterovskaia, Antonina, 1930-1938
      Box/Folder 18: 47
    - Nikita Aleksandrovich, Prince of Russia, 1930-1944
      Box/Folder 18: 48
    - Nikolai Obolenskii, Prince, 1927
      Box/Folder 18: 49
    - Nina Bagration-Mukhranskaia, Princess, 1914-1930
      Box/Folder 18: 50
    - Ol'ga Aleksandrovna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1924
      Box/Folder 18: 51
    - Ol'ga, Princess of Greece and Denmark, 1939
      Box/Folder 18: 52
    - Osluf'eva, Tat'iana, 1926-1944
      Box/Folder 18: 53
    - Orlov (Orloff), Sergei (Serge), 1924-1944
      Box/Folder 18: 54
    - Pantaleoni, A., circa 1930
      Box/Folder 18: 55
    - Peganova, Ol'ga, 1929-1938
      Box/Folder 18: 56
    - Penard, E., 1944
      Box/Folder 18: 57
    - Petkovich, Kira, 1930
      Box/Folder 18: 58
    - Pettuz, Berthe, circa 1930
      Box/Folder 18: 59
    - Petrovich, N., 1927-1930
      Box/Folder 18: 60
    - Piazhe, N., 1942
      Box/Folder 18: 61
    - Plancon, 1938
      Box/Folder 18: 62
    - Pogachnik, Branko, 1936
      Box/Folder 19: 1
    - Polychroniadis, Militsa and S., 1938
      Box/Folder 19: 2
    - Poznanskaia, Natal'ia, 1927-1930
      Box/Folder 19: 3
    - Proletov, E. and M., 1929-1930
      Box/Folder 19: 4
    - Putiatin, Mikhail and Sofia, 1920-1928
      Box/Folder 19: 5
    - Ram, Natal'ia and Mariia, 1928-1942
      Box/Folder 19: 6
    - Ramzier, Mariia, 1938-1943
      Box/Folder 19: 7
    - Rashevskaia (Rashevsky), N., 1938
      Box/Folder 19: 8
    - Reibold de la Tour, Ellen, 1944
      Box/Folder 19: 9
    - Reymond, G., 1938
      Box/Folder 19: 10
    - Remontel, Alice Van, 1944
      Box/Folder 19: 11
    - Rimskii-Korsakov, Vladimir Valer'ianovich, 1929-1930
      Box/Folder 19: 12
    - Rodesta Costa, L. A., 1938
      Box/Folder 19: 13
    - Saksonskii, Mark (Marc), 1938-1944
      Box/Folder 19: 14
    - Schulenburg, V., Count, 1938
      Box/Folder 19: 15
    - Serdakovskii, Lev., 1938-1940
      Box/Folder 19: 16
    - Shakhovskoi, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1924-1927
      Box/Folder 19: 17
    - Sheremetev, Sergei, 1944-1945
      Box/Folder 19: 18
    - Shtreker, E., 1925
      Box/Folder 19: 19
    - Shuvalova, E., 1927
      Box/Folder 19: 20
    - Simovskii, N., 1939
      Box/Folder 19: 21
    - Skrynitsin, S., 1930-1940
      Box/Folder 19: 22
    - Skuratov, Konstantin, 1928
      Box/Folder 19: 23
    - Smirnov (Smirnoff), Sergei (Serge), 1926-1938
      Box/Folder 19: 24
    - Sokolovskaia, V., 1934
      Box/Folder 19: 25
    - Solovikov (Solowikoff)-Rambach, K. N., 1924-1927
      Box/Folder 19: 26
    - Souller, G., 1924
      Box/Folder 19: 27
    - Spalaikovich, M., 1930
      Box/Folder 19: 28
    - Stefanovich, Andrei, 1927
      Box/Folder 19: 29
    - Stepanovich, Nicolas, 1928-1933
      Box/Folder 19: 30
    - Tasso, Nicolas, 1924-1938
      Box/Folder 19: 31
    - Teimuraz (Teymuraz) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) Bagration-Mukhranskii, Prince, 1926-1945 (Reels 25-26)
      Box/Folder 19: 32-34 (Folder 32 on Reel 25, Folders 33-34 on Reel 26)
    - Tereshchenko, Aleksandra and Olga, 1938-1943 (Reel 26)
      Box/Folder 19: 35
    - Thomsen, B., circa 1930
      Box/Folder 19: 36
    - Tolstaia, Zinaida, 1927
      Box/Folder 19: 37
    - Tsvechnikova, N., 1942
      Box/Folder 19: 38
    - Ugriumova, S., 1927
      Box/Folder 19: 39
    - Ukhtomskii, Nikolai, 1938
      Box/Folder 19: 40
    - Veis, S., 1938
      Box/Folder 19: 41
    - Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna), Princess of Russia, 1926-1944
      Box/Folder 19: 42-43
    - Vogard, A. M., 1930
      Box/Folder 19: 44
    - Vichkovskii, S., 1927
      Box/Folder 19: 45
    - Vrangel, Mariia, 1938
      Box/Folder 19: 46
    - Wagniere, L., 1925-1938
      Box/Folder 19: 47
    - Yaccard, Emme, 1924
      Box/Folder 19: 48
    - Zapolskii, O., 1940
      Box/Folder 19: 49
    - Zarnekai, P., 1938
      Box/Folder 19: 50
    - Zherebkova, E., 1937
      Box/Folder 19: 51
    - Zolotova, A., 1930
      Box/Folder 19: 52
    - Princess Tat'iana Konstantinovna's (Constantinovna) draft letters, 1930
      Box/Folder 19: 53-54
  - Princess Tat'iana Konstantinovna's (Constantinovna) notes regarding her children, 1926-1930
    Box/Folder 19: 55
  - Russian Orthodox Church in Paris and Geneva file, 1924-1945
    - Correspondence, 1924-1939
      Box/Folder 20: 1-7
    - Events and activities, programs, speeches, and notes, 1924-1938 (Reels 26-27)
      Box/Folder 20: 8-13 (Folder 8 on Reel 26, Folders 9-13 on Reel 27)
    - Church fundraising documents, 1944-1945 (Reel 27)
      Box/Folder 20: 14-15
  - Financial documents, 1922-1945 (Reels 27-28)
    Box/Folder 20: 16-20 (Reel 27), 21: 1-2 (Reel 28)
  - Clippings on art and politics, 1938-1939 (Reel 28)
    Box/Folder 21: 3-4
- Princess Tat'iana Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) papers from red trunk no. 5, 1928-1980
  - Correspondence, 1928-1942
    - Antonii, Metropolitan, circa 1929
      Box/Folder 21: 5
    - Dmitrii Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Grand Duke of Russia, 1928
      Box/Folder 21: 6
    - Rahm, Robert, 1941-1942
      Box/Folder 21: 7
    - Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna), Princess of Russia, 1938
      Box/Folder 21: 8
  - Notebook, 1928
    Box/Folder 21: 9
    Includes copy of a letter from Grand Duke Andrei Vladimirovich of Russia about the false Anastasia.
  - Death of Abbess Tamara, née Princess Tat'iana Konstantinovna of Russia, 1979-1980
    - Obituaries, 1979
      Box/Folder 21: 10-12
    - Condolence letters to Prince Teimuraz (Teymuraz) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) Bagration-Mukhranskii on the death of his mother, 1979-1980 (Reels 28-29)
      Box/Folder 21: 13-16 (Folders 13-15 on Reel 28, Folder 16 on Reel 29)
- Prince Konstantin (Constantin) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) Bagration-Mukhranskii letters to his parents from red trunk no. 6, 1900-1919 (Reel 29)
  Box/Folder 21: 17
- Princess Natal'ia Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) Bagration-Mukhranskaia-Johnston correspondence from red trunk no. 6, 1925-1934
  - General, 1929-1933
    Box/Folder 21: 18
  - Elizaveta Mavrikievna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1928-1933
    Box/Folder 21: 19
  - Gavriil (Gabriel) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, 1933
    Box/Folder 21: 20
  - Irinei, Bishop, 1929
    Box/Folder 21: 21
  - Litovets, L., circa 1925
    Box/Folder 21: 22
  - Marina, Princess of Greece and Denmark, 1933
    Box/Folder 21: 23
  - Marina Petrovna, Princess of Russia, 1933
    Box/Folder 21: 24
  - Nesterovskaia, Antonina Rafailovna, 1927
    Box/Folder 22: 1
  - Sheremetev, Sergei, 1930
    Box/Folder 22: 2
  - Smirnov (Smirnoff), Sergei (Serge), 1931-1933
    Box/Folder 22: 3
  - Teimuraz (Teymuraz) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich) Bagration-Mukhranskii, Prince, 1927-1934
    Box/Folder 22: 4-6
  - Vera Konstantinovna (Constantinovna), Princess of Russia, 1927
    Box/Folder 22: 7
- Princess Tat'iana Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) papers from red trunk no. 6, 1847-1991
  - Correspondence, 1911-1945
    - General, 1927-1945
      Box/Folder 22: 8-11
    - Adamovich, Boris, 1930-1931
      Box/Folder 22: 12
    - Adelheid, Cousine, 1942-1944
      Box/Folder 22: 13
    - Alexander I of Yugoslavia, 1922-1928
      Box/Folder 22: 14
    - Aleksei (Alexis) Bagration, Prince, 1942
      Box/Folder 22: 15
    - Anastasiia, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1924
      Box/Folder 22: 16
    - Anastasii, Metropolitan, 1940
      Box/Folder 22: 17
    - Asperlin, Gaston le Rothien, 1940-1942
      Box/Folder 22: 18
    - Bacheracht, A. de, 1924
      Box/Folder 22: 19
    - Baltazzi, Sofie A., 1926
      Box/Folder 22: 20
    - Benua, Aleksandr (Alexandre et Kama Benois), 1924-1940
      Box/Folder 22: 21
    - Boni, Nina, 1924-1925
      Box/Folder 22: 22
    - Bossar, Eugeniia, 1941-1942
      Box/Folder 22: 23
    - Butovich, Iulia, 1924-1933
      Box/Folder 22: 24
    - Candolle, Lurize de, 1937-1943
      Box/Folder 22: 25
    - Le Comité international de la Croix-Rouge, 1939-1942
      Box/Folder 22: 26
    - Cort, D. and J., 1942
      Box/Folder 22: 27
    - Dadiani, Elisso, 1942
      Box/Folder 22: 28
    - Deonna, Edmee, 1942
      Box/Folder 22: 29
    - Dukhonina, Natal'ia, 1933-1940
      Box/Folder 22: 30
    - Dumitrescu-Doletti, Joanna, 1942-1945
      Box/Folder 22: 31-32
    - Elisabeth, Princess of Greece and Denmark, 1942-1943
      Box/Folder 22: 33
    - Elizaveta Mavrikievna, Grand Duchess of Russia, 1924
      Box/Folder 22: 34
    - Fisher, Evgeniia, 1942-1944 (Reel 30)
      Box/Folder 22: 35
    - Gavriil (Gabriel) Konstantinovich (Constantinovich), Prince of Russia, 1924-1943
      Box/Folder 22: 36
    - Gebzattel, S., 1922-1924
      Box/Folder 22: 37
    - Geyger, Putzy
      Box/Folder 22: 38
    - Glaser, Aleksandra Andreevna, 1940-1943
      Box/Folder 22: 39
    - Heitzmann, Gabriel, 1940-1942
      Box/Folder 22: 40
    - Helen, Princess of Serbia, 1940-1942
      Box/Folder 22: 41
    - Hoffmann, Helen, 1943
      Box/Folder 22: 42
    - Horneffer, S. Ch., 1940-1942
      Box/Folder 22: 43
    - Ignat'ev, L., 1923-1940
      Box/Folder 22: 44
    - Iraklii (Irakli) Bagration, Prince of Mukhrani, 1940-1942
      Box/Folder 22: 45
    - Kallash, M., 1924
      Box/Folder 22: 46
    - Kantakuzin, Konstantin and Ekaterina (Katia), 1922-1940
      Box/Folder 22: 47
    - Koiander, Varvara, 1924
      Box/Folder 22: 48
    - Kolcheff, Leonid, 1921-1924
      Box/Folder 22: 49
    - Komisarzhevskii (Komisarjevsky), Ernestina and Theodore, 1940-1945
      Box/Folder 23: 1
    - Korochentsov (Korochentzoff), Aleksei and Lilly, 1924-1940
      Box/Folder 23: 2-3
    - Laiming, Aleksandr and Ol'ga, 1922-1924
      Box/Folder 23: 4
    - Lebedeva, Anna, 1940
      Box/Folder 23: 5
    - Lefort, R., 1924-1942
      Box/Folder 23: 6
    - La Légation Royale de Yougoslavie en Suisse, 1942
      Box/Folder 23: 7
    - Leonidova, Elena, 1926
      Box/Folder 23: 8
    - Lipsky, D. de, 1942
      Box/Folder 23: 9
    - Maksimova, Elena, 1924-1935
      Box/Folder 23: 10
    - Maria Feodorovna, Dowager Empress of Russia, 1924-1925
      Box/Folder 23: 11
    - Meuron, Isabella de, 1942-1944
      Box/Folder 23: 12
    - Miautin, M., 1922
      Box/Folder 23: 13
    - Mikhail Volkonskii, Prince, 1930
      Box/Folder 23: 14
    - Mitchell (Edgley), Maria M., 1937-1942
      Box/Folder 23: 15-16
    - Montenegro, Vera, circa 1930
      Box/Folder 23: 17
    - Murav'eva-Apostol, N., 1933-1942
      Box/Folder 23: 18
    - Natal'ia Konstantinovna (Constantinovna) Bagration-Mukhranskaia-Johnston, Princess, 1927-1940 (Reels 30-31)
      Box/Folder 23: 19-26 (Folders 19-20 on Reel 30, Folders 21-26 on Reel 31), 24: 1-2 (on Reel 31)